MARKS UNGEITIS

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



PROFILE

I am a dedicated and skilled Software Engineer with over 4 years of hands-on experience in developing web applications. My expertise lies in utilizing React and Redux to manage state efficiently, as well as creating visually appealing designs using Figma.

SKILLS

- React / Next.js / Angular
- TypeScript
- Redux / Redux Thunk
- Node.JS / Express / AWS
- Material-UI /EPAM UUI
- Figma / Jira / Git
- Jest / Cypress
- Al Promt Engineering

EDUCATION

BARCHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

Liepajas Valsts Tehnikums 2020-2024

LANGUAGES

Russian Latvian English Native Native B1+

CONTACT

+371 20089550 markekungeitis@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (CONTRACT)

EPAM Systems (2024 - Present)

- Develop new features and maintain existing
- Add API integrations
- Optimize application for maximum speed and include responsive design
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams, including designers, backend developers, and product managers
- Planing future work and new features
- Fix defects/bugs and investigate root cause of issues
- Write unit tests and e2e tests
- Maintain components for the Storybook

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Fon Control Group (2022 - 2024)

- Develop new features and maintain existing
- Add API integrations
- Fix defects/bugs and investigate root cause of issues
- Write unit tests and e2e tests
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams, including designers, backend developers, and product managers